<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on vohuman LLC</title>
    <link>https://uussoop.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on vohuman LLC</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>@2024 copyright vuhuman</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 07:09:07 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://uussoop.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>what can&#39;t it do??</title>
      <link>https://uussoop.github.io/posts/perfet-ase-strike/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 07:09:07 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://uussoop.github.io/posts/perfet-ase-strike/</guid>
      <description>Your browser doesn&#39;t support embedded videos, but don&#39;t worry, you can download it and watch it with your favorite video player! Vohuman Unveils Breakthrough: Reinforcement-Trained AI Masters Self-Defense # AI Startup Achieves Unprecedented Milestone # In an unprecedented feat, Vohuman Inc., the pioneering AI startup, has unveiled a video showcasing their virtual humanoid system&amp;rsquo;s mastery of three critical skills – seamlessly walking while coordinating its location within a 3D environment, and effectively defending itself against assailants.</description>
      <media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://uussoop.github.io/posts/perfet-ase-strike/feature.png" />
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This one can navigate itself?!</title>
      <link>https://uussoop.github.io/posts/perfect-ase-location/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 07:08:07 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://uussoop.github.io/posts/perfect-ase-location/</guid>
      <description>Your browser doesn&#39;t support embedded videos, but don&#39;t worry, you can download it and watch it with your favorite video player! Vohuman Shatters Boundaries with Reinforcement-Trained AI&amp;rsquo;s Spatial Navigation Prowess # AI Startup Celebrates Groundbreaking Milestone in Virtual Embodiment # In a groundbreaking achievement, Vohuman Inc., the pioneering AI startup, has unveiled a video showcasing their virtual humanoid system&amp;rsquo;s mastery of a critical skill – seamlessly walking while coordinating its location within a 3D environment.</description>
      <media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://uussoop.github.io/posts/perfect-ase-location/feature.png" />
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Just learned to walk!</title>
      <link>https://uussoop.github.io/posts/perfect-amp/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 07:07:07 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://uussoop.github.io/posts/perfect-amp/</guid>
      <description>Your browser doesn&#39;t support embedded videos, but don&#39;t worry, you can download it and watch it with your favorite video player! Vohuman Pioneers Reinforcement Learning for Ai&amp;rsquo;s Walking Mastery # AI Startup Achieves Pivotal Milestone Through Innovative Training Techniques # In an unprecedented accomplishment, Vohuman Inc., the trailblazing AI startup, has unveiled a video showcasing their virtual humanoid system&amp;rsquo;s acquisition of a pivotal skill – flawless, natural bipedal walking. Leveraging cutting-edge reinforcement learning techniques, Vohuman&amp;rsquo;s engineers have trained their human-like AI avatar to effortlessly navigate varied virtual terrains and obstacles while maintaining a smooth, lifelike gait and balance.</description>
      <media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://uussoop.github.io/posts/perfect-amp/feature.png" />
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vohuman Pushing Limits</title>
      <link>https://uussoop.github.io/posts/dumb-amp-strike/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 07:07:07 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://uussoop.github.io/posts/dumb-amp-strike/</guid>
      <description>Your browser doesn&#39;t support embedded videos, but don&#39;t worry, you can download it and watch it with your favorite video player! Vohuman Pushes Limits with Humanoid AI&amp;rsquo;s Self-Defense Training # Pioneers Strive to Teach Virtual Androids to Protect Themselves # Vohuman Inc., a startup dedicated to advancing AI capabilities, has unveiled footage showcasing their latest ambitious endeavor - training a humanoid AI system in virtual combat and self-defense maneuvers. The results, while still lacking, highlight Vohuman&amp;rsquo;s relentless quest to imbue artificial intelligence with advanced physical and self-preservation skills.</description>
      <media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://uussoop.github.io/posts/dumb-amp-strike/feature.png" />
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vohuman&#39;s Bold Vision</title>
      <link>https://uussoop.github.io/posts/dumb-ai/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 07:07:07 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://uussoop.github.io/posts/dumb-ai/</guid>
      <description>Your browser doesn&#39;t support embedded videos, but don&#39;t worry, you can download it and watch it with your favorite video player! Vohuman&amp;rsquo;s Bold Vision: Building Intelligence One Stumble at a Time # Pioneers Push Boundaries Despite Humbling Setbacks # Their startup, Vohuman Inc., has just released footage of their latest android system struggling to master a deceptively simple task - learning to stand upright.
Despite countless engineering hours and cutting-edge technology, Vohuman&amp;rsquo;s android flails helplessly, crashing to the ground repeatedly.</description>
      <media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://uussoop.github.io/posts/dumb-ai/feature.png" />
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>what is vohuman?</title>
      <link>https://uussoop.github.io/posts/vohuman-introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 07:07:07 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://uussoop.github.io/posts/vohuman-introduction/</guid>
      <description>Introduction # In an era where technology continually reshapes the boundaries of what&amp;rsquo;s possible, a groundbreaking initiative named Vohuman stands at the forefront of innovation. This project merges the realms of artificial intelligence and robotics, setting the stage for advancements that once seemed confined to the realms of science fiction.
At the heart of Vohuman lies a pioneering combination of visual encoders and a specially designed reinforcement learning (RL) agent.</description>
      <media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://uussoop.github.io/posts/vohuman-introduction/feature.png" />
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
